Tang Phuoc Quang

Software Engineer

♦ https://jam3shalliday.github.io/pv2/

SUMMARY

Hi, I'm Quang, 2000, a front-end developer with two years of experience, familiar with reactjs and its ecosystem, able to work as a full stack developer with nodejs, experienced working in e-commerce, insurance and health-tech field. This time, I'm looking for a job where I can expand my skills more in both front-end and back-end.

SKILLS

Familiar with some front-end likes: reactis, nextis, mui, redux-toolkit, tailwindcss, ... some knowledge in back-end: mongodb, nodejs, express, sql. and some other tools: git, figma, notion, linux, vscode, ...

WORK EXPERIENCES

free!

April 2023 - Present

Buymed | Thuocsi.vn

June 2022 - April 2023

I'm currently having a break between jobs, taking time to read some books, and self-taught some more skills about micro front-end, express, database, ci/cd, and deployment.

Front end developer

Project: Circa.vn (circa.vn - in development)

An e-commerce web-application provide end-user a solution to buy medicine, connect multiple providers to customer without "sold-out" problem.

Technologies: typescript, nextjs, tailwindcss, redux-toolkit, mui, ... **Description:**

- As a founding engineer of the team, my responsible was designing, and structuring a scalable and maintainable source base for front-end using nextjs and typescript.
- Collaborated with design team and back-end team to continuously deliver the product.
- Participating in peer code review to obtain the highest quality code possible.
- · Researching and implementing libraries.

Project: POS (https://pos.circa.vn)

An internal project for managing pharmacy products in-store, online and offline sales, statistics, and more ...

Technologies: typescript, nextjs, tailwindcss, redux-toolkit, mui, ... **Description:**

- Designing, and structuring a scalable and maintainable source base
- Worked closely with Product Manager, receive requirements, and delivered production code on time.
- · Research and implement APIs and libraries.
- · Collaborated with the internal back-end team and other external teams for integrating API and resources.

Goalist Co.,Ltd.

July 2021 - Feb 2022

Front end developer

Project: Jopus connecter LP (https://connecter.jopus.net/en/)

A recruitment platform service specialized for foreigners looking for work in Japan.

Technologies: HTML, SASS, ...

Description:

- Revamping the application user interface using HTML, sass, and js to significantly improve the user experience.
- Worked closely to design team from Japan, continuously updating and delivery product on time.

Casting Road (https://hr-visual.jp)

A B2B platform provides companies data and statistics of other companies compared together.

Technologies: reactjs, nextjs, typescript, spring, mysql, hibernate, ... **Description**:

- · Assisted the senior developers by coding and contributed to fixing bugs.
- Implement socket on front-end to receive events passively
- Implement new features following design and requirements.

Hrog (https://hrog.co.jp)

Technologies: markdown, goHugo, HTML SCSS

Description:

 Creating and managing contents of CMS using markdown, HTML and Gohugo

Savemoney Corporation

May 2020 - May 2021

Full-stack developer

Project: Insurwin / Insurtech

B2B and B2C platforms provide a solution for insurance companies and customers, able to buy insurance easily, simplify paperwork and many middle-step

Technologies: javascript, typeScript, reactJs, umiJs, redux, express, sequelize, graphql, microservice, RESTful, PostgreSQL

Description:

- Participating in daily scrum meetings, sprint planning, and bug fixes.
- Performed code review, work closely with team members to ensure consistency with code standards.
- Hands-on experience as a full-stack developer
- Developing the CRUD for Rest API calls, to fetch, and store data.
- Creating tables, indexes, migrating, export and import of data.

CERTIFICATIONS

Apr 2020

Cybersoft's Front end development degree.

EDUCATION

Cybersoft Academy

Dec 2019 - Apr 2020

Major: Front end web development.

Learn basic front end development by building some simple project from scratch using react and some related technologies, ...

Cao Thang Technical College

Sep 2018 - Nov 2019

Major: Networking Management.

Studied internet, hardwares, Windows, config network and C++ programming.

INTERESTING

Currently I'm having some interesting in research more front-end technologies, animations and web apis, reading some books and novels, playing some games, every day practicing calisthenic and meditation.

Thank you very much for taking your time on my resume.

Have a nice day!